Full Menu
---------

        * [Elementary and Secondary School Emergency Relief (ESSER) III - Plan for Safe Return](https://www.fcps.edu/ESSER3)
        * [Strategic Plan Goal 2 - Safe, Supported, Included, and Empowered](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps/strategic-plan-2023-30/strategic-plan-goal-2-safe-supported-included-and-empowered)
        * [Strategic Plan Goal 4 in Action - Equitable Access and Opportunity](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps/strategic-plan-2023-30/strategic-plan-goal-4-action-equitable-access-and-opportunity)
        * [Strategic Plan Goal 5 in Action - Leading for Tomorrow's Innovation](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps/strategic-plan-2023-30/strategic-plan-goal-5-action-leading-tomorrows-innovation)
            * [Advanced Academic Programs (AAP) - Level IV Screening Process](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/advanced-academic-programs-aap/advanced-academic-programs-aap-level-iv)
            * [Orientation Information for Full-Time Advanced Academic Programs (AAP)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/advanced-academic-programs/orientation)
            * [Review of the Fairfax County Public Schools Advanced Academic Programs Executive Summary](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/advanced-academic-programs-aap/review-fairfax-county-public-schools)
            * [Multi-tiered Systems of Support (MTSS)/Responsive Instruction (RI)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/special-education-instruction/multi-tiered-systems-support)
                * [Earning an Applied Studies Diploma (Career and Transition Services)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/special-education-instruction/career-and-transition-services/earning)
                * [Assistive Technology Support for Students with Reading Difficulties](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/special-education-instruction/assistive-technology-services-ats-2)
            * [Education for Employment (EFE)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/academic-overview/special-education-instruction/career-and-transition-services/education-for-employment "Education for Employment (EFE)")
            * [Determining Quarter and Final Grades (Secondary Grading and Reporting)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/grading-and-reporting/secondary/determining-quarter-and-final-grades)
            * [Grading Assignments and Assessments (Secondary Grading and Reporting)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/grading-and-reporting/secondary/grading-assignments-and-assessments)
        * [Graduation Requirements: First Time Ninth Graders in 2018-2019 and Beyond](https://www.fcps.edu/graduation-requirements-and-course-planning/first-time-ninth-2018-19)
            * [Advanced Placement (AP)/International Baccalaureate (IB) Test Fees](https://www.fcps.edu/testfees)
        * [Camps and Institutes: Elementary Institute for the Arts (E-IFTA)](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/summer-learning-programs/camps-and-institutes-elementary-institute-arts-e-ifta)
        * [Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Summer Learning Opportunities](https://www.fcps.edu/academics/summer-learning/thomas-jefferson-high-school-science-and-technology-summer-learning)
        * [Adding, Changing, or Removing an Instructional Licensure Endorsement(s)](https://www.fcps.edu/careers/instructional-licensure/adding-changing-or-removing-instructional-licensure-endorsements)
        * [Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Admissions](https://www.fcps.edu/department/thomas-jefferson-high-school-science-and-technology-admissions-office)
            * [Apprenticeships and Training - College and Postsecondary Options](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/college-and-career-planning/college-and-post-secondary-planning/apprenticeships-training)
            * [Financial Aid and Scholarships - College and Postsecondary Options](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/college-and-career-planning/college-and-post-secondary-planning/financial-aid)
            * [Test Preparation Resources - College and Postsecondary Options](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/college-and-career-planning/college-and-post-secondary-planning/test-preparation)
        * [Booster Club, PTA/PTO Managed, Fee-Based Classes, Clinics, Leagues, and Youth Camps](https://www.fcps.edu/clubs-classes-clinics-leagues-and-youth-camps)
            * [Đường dây Điện thoại Cung cấp Thông tin cho Phụ huynh của FCPS](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/family-engagement/parent-information-phone-lines/vietnamese)
            * [خطوط هواتف مدارس مقاطعة فيرفاكس الحكومية لاستعلامات أولياء الأمور](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/family-engagement/parent-information-phone-lines/arabic)
        * [Gun Violence - Student Support Resources and FCPS Safety Practices](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/student-safety-and-wellness/gun-violence-student-support-resources-and-fcps-safety)
        * [Bring Your Own Device (BYOD)](https://www.fcps.edu/resources/technology/bring-your-own-device-byod "Bring Your Own Device (BYOD)")
            * [Workforce Development Partnerships (including STEM and STEAM)](https://www.fcps.edu/get-involved/business-and-community-partnerships/ignite-partnerships/workforce-development "Workforce Development Partnerships (including STEM and STEAM)")
        * [Advanced Academics Identification and Placement for Students New to FCPS Boundaries](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/advanced-academics-identification-and-placement/students-new-fcps)
        * [For Students New to FCPS Boundaries (Including Military Families)](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/advanced-academics-identification-and-placement/students-new-fcps)
        * [Family Relocation (A) Prior to Relocation into Requested School Boundary - Student Transfer Application](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/student-transfer-information/family-relocation-prior-relocation-requested-school)
        * [Family Relocation (B) for Remainder of School Year - Student Transfer Application](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/student-transfer-information/family-relocation-b-remainder-school-year-student)
        * [High School Curricular Program (AP, IB and World Languages) - Student Transfer Application](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/student-transfer-information/high-school-curricular-program-ap-ib-and-world-languages)
        * [Medical, Emotional, or Social Adjustment Student - Student Transfer Application](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/student-transfer-information/medical-emotional-or-social-adjustment-student-student)
        * [Resident on Military Installation - Student Transfer Application](https://www.fcps.edu/registration/student-transfer-information/resident-military-installation-student-transfer)
    * [Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology Admissions](https://www.fcps.edu/tjadmissions)

[Fairfax County Public Schools
=============================](https://www.fcps.edu/ "Home")

76°F

Overcast clouds

* [Español](javascript:Drupal.doFCPSGTranslate('en|es'))
* [한국어](javascript:Drupal.doFCPSGTranslate('en|ko'))
* [中文](javascript:Drupal.doFCPSGTranslate('en|zh-CN'))
* [Tiếng Việt](javascript:Drupal.doFCPSGTranslate('en|vi'))
* [العربية](javascript:Drupal.doFCPSGTranslate('en|ar'))

Close

Main Menu
---------

Search FCPS 

Search FCPS 

Footer
------

Breadcrumb
----------

1. [Fairfax County Public Schools](https://www.fcps.edu/)
2. [About FCPS](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps)
3. [Policies, Regulations, and Notices](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps/policies-regulations-and-notices)
4. Web Privacy Policy

Web Privacy Policy
==================

How FCPS gathers information on our web site and with whom and under what conditions we share this information.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

It is the policy of the Commonwealth of Virginia that personal information about citizens will be collected only to the extent necessary to provide the service or benefit desired; that only appropriate information will be collected; and that the citizen shall understand the reason the information is collected and be able to examine his or her personal record that is maintained by Fairfax County Public Schools (FCPS).

The following is intended to explain the division’s current Internet privacy practices but shall not be construed as a contractual promise. FCPS reserves the right to amend its Internet privacy policy statement at any time without notice.

Information Collection
----------------------

Virginia law requires that state bodies not collect personal information about citizens unless it is required to provide services for the citizen. When personal information is collected, it must be protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, and FCPS is required to provide a prescribed procedure by which individuals may learn the purpose for which information has been recorded and how the agency will use and disseminate it.

In General
----------

FCPS does not capture personal information about any visitor to its site without his or her permission. When you browse the FCPS web site without logging on to any of the interactive online services, you do so anonymously. Personal information, such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, is not collected as you browse. Information, such as your domain name, Internet protocol number, browser type, and date and time of your visit, is collected but not tied to your personal identity. FCPS uses this information to track the number of customers who visit the site and to identify the most popular pages so that the division can improve site content and accessibility.

Online Transactions
-------------------

Personal information that you provide to FCPS is safeguarded according to the laws of Virginia.

Personal information required either by law or in order for FCPS to provide a requested service is subject to the requirements for administering information systems as established in the [Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act, Chapter 38 of Title 2.2](http://law.lis.virginia.gov/vacode/title2.2/chapter38/section2.2-3803/) of the Code of Virginia. Personal information is only requested at this site when needed to complete various transactions with FCPS online and for FCPS to deliver the requested services. FCPS only collects, retains, and uses personal information when it believes it is essential, and allowed by law, to conduct business and provide products and services. Should you not want to provide the requested personal information, FCPS will not be able to provide you with online services.

Surveys
-------

Information that you provide on online surveys is used to improve the programs and services that FCPS offers. This information is not stored with any other records FCPS may have of your interactions with the school system.

Contacting Us
-------------

When visiting the site, FCPS encourages you to contact us if you have any questions, comments, or concerns. The information provided is used solely to respond to your inquiry. Personal information that you provide to FCPS is safeguarded according to the laws of Virginia .

Information Access
------------------

Any personal information that is collected and retained by FCPS is maintained in compliance with the [Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act, Chapter 38 of Title 2.2](http://law.lis.virginia.gov/vacode/title2.2/chapter38/section2.2-3803/) of the Code of Virginia. The agency does not share, sell, or trade e-mail addresses, information collected on surveys, or any other information about its online customers to any entity except as provided for or required by the Government Data Collection and Dissemination Act, the [Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), Chapter 37 of Title 2.2](http://law.lis.virginia.gov/vacode/title2.2/chapter37/section2.2-3700/), or other law. Under FOIA, any records in FCPS’ possession at the time of a FOIA request might be subject to being inspected by or disclosed to members of the public, unless the FOIA specifically allows FCPS to keep the records confidential. If necessary, FCPS may disclose user information if it has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against an individual who attempts, even unintentionally, to access FCPS information without authorization or to disrupt the FCPS web site.

Use of Cookies
--------------

In certain applications, user information is stored as cookies, which are then sent back and stored on your hard drive. Cookies allow the agency to save the information that you input while progressing through an online transaction. If your browser is not configured to accept cookies, you will still be able to access the information on the web site, but you may not be able to complete many of the online transactions. No user information is gathered through cookies except for that needed to run the specific application.

Security
--------

FCPS maintains security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information to prevent unauthorized removal or alteration of data. When you browse public areas of the FCPS web site, none of your personal information is captured or stored by the school system. FCPS protects its records in accordance with its obligations as defined by applicable Virginia statutes--including, but not limited to, the Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act and the Virginia Freedom of Information Act--and by any applicable federal laws.

Information Accuracy and Your Rights
------------------------------------

FCPS has established procedures to ensure that information is as accurate and current as is practical to enable the school system to conduct business with you. You have the right to review any record that FCPS maintains about you in order to verify its accuracy. You may do this by contacting the individual curator listed in conjunction with any application at this web site.

Disclaimer
----------

Fairfax County Public Schools provides links to web sites that are not controlled, maintained, or regulated by FCPS or any organization affiliated with FCPS, and, as such, FCPS is not responsible for the content of those web sites. Use of information obtained from those web sites is voluntary, and reliance on that information should only be undertaken after an independent review of its accuracy. Reference at those web sites to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or preference by FCPS. The school division tries to screen all sites included on its web site but cannot control the content they possess.

Footer
------

Footer Meta Menu
----------------

* [Freedom of Information Act](https://www.fcps.edu/about-fcps/policies-regulations-and-notices/virginia-freedom-information-act-vfoia "The Virginia Freedom of Information Act (VFOIA)")

Follow FCPS on Social Media
---------------------------

Social Media in Español (Spanish)
---------------------------------

Social Media in 한국어 (Korean)
----------------------------

©Copyright 2024 Fairfax County School Board. All Rights Reserved.

This site requires JavaScript to be enabled in order to run.
